The story that shocked the country.
Native Son is a drama film directed by Jerrold Freedman.
In 1940s Chicago, a young black man takes a job as a chauffeur to a white family, which takes a turn for the
worse when he accidentally kills the teenage daughter of the couple and then tries to cover it up.
Bigger Thomas, played by Victor Love.
Jan, played by Matt Dillon.
Mary Dalton, played by Elizabeth McGovern.
Peggy, played by Geraldine Page.
Mrs. Thomas, played by Oprah Winfrey.
Bessie, played by Akosua Busia.
Native Son is a 1986 American drama film directed by Jerrold Freeman, and
starring Carroll Baker, Victor Love, Matt Dillon and Oprah Winfrey.
The film is based on the 1940 novel Native Son, written by Richard Wright.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois, chauffeur,
based on novel or book, paranoia, racial tension.
The tone is emotional.